{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": 2001,
            "question": "Is Javascript case-sensitive ?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "A",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2002,
            "question": "Is Javascript the same as is Java ?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2003,
            "question": "Is C# the same as is C++ ?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2004,
            "question": "Could a semicolon be used in brainfuck?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2005,
            "question": "Is it possible to create HelloWorld in javascript using only six characters? (not code length)",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y - JsFuck",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2006,
            "question": "Has a Holly supercomputer from IQ 8000 ? (Which is like 8,000 gym teachers)",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - 6000",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2007,
            "question": "Was google the first search engine in internet?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Archie",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2008,
            "question": "Is Firewall in computer used for Authentication?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Security",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2009,
            "question": "Is COBOL a database management software?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2010,
            "question": "Is .gif an extension for videos?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2011,
            "question": " Is WordStar the first word processor application?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2012,
            "question": "Is RAM volatile memory in a computer system?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2013,
            "question": "One Terabyte (1 TB) is equal to 1000GB",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - 1024GB",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2014,
            "question": "Was Windows the first fully supported 64-bit operating system?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Linux",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2015,
            "question": "Is MOSAIC a web browser ?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2016,
            "question": "Is Trojan a computer virus ?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Malware",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2017,
            "question": "Is SMTP Protocol used to receive an e-mail?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Pop3",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2018,
            "question": "Is Pop3 Protocol used to receive an e-mail?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2019,
            "question": "Was '@' sign first chosen for its use in e-mail address before 1975?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y - 1972",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2020,
            "question": "Is monitor an Input device ?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - output",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2021,
            "question": "Is Firefox used as an search engine?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - it's browser",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2022,
            "question": "Are cookies stored on the server?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - on the client",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2023,
            "question": "Antivirus protect systems from hackers",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Firewall",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2024,
            "question": "USB Hard disk is a secondary type of storage device",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2025,
            "question": "'IoT' refers to - Internet Organisation of Telecommunication",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Internet of Things",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2026,
            "question": "Who is a shared resource for both Camio and Axis.",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y ",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2027,
            "question": "Does Jim Martinolich own a boat?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2028,
            "question": "Is the September 11 attack (2001) the reason why the development of the first ever version of Maps module got postponed?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2029,
            "question": "Is Jirka a singer?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2030,
            "question": "Is the number of created Jira work items created since Dec 14th 2020 in the Axis project higher than 1000?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2031,
            "question": "Is Patrik proficient in martial arts?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2032,
            "question": "Is Patrikâ€™s dog named Kevin?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Merlin",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2033,
            "question": "Are Maps the most used module in Axis by the entire customer group?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "N - Order",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2034,
            "question": "Are Quotes the least used module in Axis by the entire customer group?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Y",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2035,
            "question": "Is .NET 5 direct successor of .NET 4.7.2?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "No, it is direct successor of .NET Core",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2036,
            "question": "Is Transport Tycoon part of the Axis?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "No",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2037,
            "question": "Do we have a monorepo?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Yes (Axis repository)",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2038,
            "question": "Do we have some part of axis (incuding infrastructure) runing on Cloud?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Yes (Configuration harvestor)",
            "winner": null
        },
        {
            "id": 2039,
            "question": "Is age difference between Martin's kids more than 13yo?",
            "hint": "Y/N",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "winner": null
        }
    ]
}